Thanks for watching!
Here's the video from earlier only.
Oh, wait a minute.
You're trying to see me laugh and smile?
Just a second.
It's kind of drawn out.
Touch it. It's tight.
It really is.
Want to try loosening it later?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Gorgeous.
It's so clean.
Um, today...
Everyone today.
Thank you.
If you don't stop a little bit longer.
I'm going to fall off.
So we can have a conversation.
Hey, people.
You're in the library.
LOL.
What's up?
Pio's hair, his hair.
LOL!
I have to make hair.
I got it.
Thank you!
Now I have more trust in you.
I'm so happy!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
What a totally different view!
Oh, it feels super nice.
Thank you.
I only have my glasses
Pleasure.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, one.
We're Jou!
Se-no, go!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, please.
Here you go.
Okay, I'm ready.
I don't know what to do.
Thank you for your hard work.
Congratulations.
Look, basa style.
Good evening.
Look, it's tacky.
Lame.
Dumb style.
Oh, it's crisp.
Thank you very much.
I got some kind of interesting shape.
Sunburn.
Thank you for watching.
That's a lot of smoke.
Hey, it's flowing.
Can we go outside?
Smoke?
Yeah, sure.
Don't go out there. Don't go out there.
Hey.
Good evening. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, the venue is at 4:00 and the show starts at 5:00. Good evening.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I look forward to it.
Looking forward to it.
I'll look forward to it.
I'm almost there! I'll do my best!
Yay!
Hello! We are A.U.C.K.Y!
We are Rekina Break Time Girls!
We will be the opening act today. We are looking forward to seeing you!
Thank you very much for your support!
We will do our best!
Yes!
Rock on!
You were so cute!
I got a towel and a message.
I was so happy.
Thank you so much!
I will use the towel with care.
I will take it to my lessons.
I will take it to my lessons, and I will also be allowed to observe the live performance,
I will use the towel and swing it around and have fun.
I will learn a lot while having fun.
I will do my best!
You are so cute!
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the show.
Please help me out!
You are so cute!
Are you with A.U.C.K.Y?
Yes, they are.
Amazing!
So cute!
I bet someone would look so good in this outfit.
I think so.
I don't think we could wear this.
It definitely looks good on you.
It's cute.
Please do.
That's all for now.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
I have an opening tomorrow on my insta story,
Thank you.
Too shy.
Cute.
I look forward to working with you again.
Thank you for your hard work.
Have a safe trip home.
I was most looking forward to what was to come after this.
I said it was the most.
I was looking forward to it the most.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Even though it was fun.
Thank you very much.
Come on, let's lengthen your legs.
That's more than enough.
That was so much fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Everyone was so warm.
I was so happy that they danced with me.
More than I expected.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
I am looking forward to it.
I will go, I will go.
I worked hard.
Thank you very much.
You are so cute.
I can do my best.
I look forward to working with you.
I've worked hard.
Thank you.
He's cute.
Interesting.
Thank you very much.
Se-no, I like it!
I love it.
Se-no, my name is Prince!
Oh my god! I'm shouting!
Oh, no! I can see it!
Oh, excuse me!
Excuse me!
Oh, my God! This is so much fun!
I kind of want you to stay out of the sun during Memories.
You know what I mean?
So cute!
They're so cute!
I'm feeling a little uplifted.
Oh, everyone?
Please!
Kanami! Junior! Hitoko! Maruko! Aki! Hiyori!
Chakki! Chizuru! Umachan!
Shokotan! Mizukingu! Super-teki-mekki full booth!
Six people!
Let's do our best!
Please come on!
Let's have fun!
Please do it!
Kanami first!
Funny!
Falling! Falling!
Should I just keep following you?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll take care of number two.
Oh, my God! That's great!
Okay, please!
Today,
Super-tekimeki publicity for
"Tokimeki Haru no Haretaibutai 2023" (The Sunny Stage of Spring 2023)
Love! I gotta have it! No, no, no!
Thank you very much for coming to
Thank you very much.
My name is Kanami, a super tecchimeki blue
This is my Kanami.
Thank you very much.
Before the show begins,
I would like to ask our guests to please pay oblique attention
at the recording free time attention meeting.
Photography in the venue is also
Please do not take pictures or drawings in the hall.
Please be aware of this before the performance begins.
This performance,
Thank you very much. Good reply.
Excessive jumping is prohibited.
Great!
Amazing!
Cute.
For guests who are seated,
No standing up to watch the show.
The show will begin shortly.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Are you ready to have some fun?
It's going to be great.
Everybody, lots of love!
Please give us a lot of love!
See you soon,
I'll be waiting for you.
From Keyarashu.
Kanami, Junior,
Hitoko, Aki,
Chiwari, super thrilling blurb,
Recording!
They responded better than I expected.
Oh, I did that one. Did I do that one?
What's that? Who's that?
He's got good feet there.
Ta-da!
One minute to go.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm moved.
I'm so happy
Thank you for watching!
Wow! Oh my God!
30 seconds to go!
That's fast!
Oh, my God!
Okay, we're almost there.
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three!
Tomorrow!
Tomorrow for the rest of my life!
Tomorrow for the rest of your life!
The best
me
The reason we were able to perform today is thanks to you, Sennen Mai, who is watching us in front of the screen.
I am really looking forward to the day when I can see you all again so that this connection will not be interrupted.
I love you so much, even when I don't see you!
Subscribe to my channel!
me
Yes, I'm a super-taxi-centered aon. With aon, the super-taxi-centive,
Kieber and Kieber
Yes, I'm Hanane. This is Hanane, my Hanane.
I'm really happy to hear everyone's voice already.
Thank you very much. Can we get excited?
Thank you very much.
I am very happy to be able to come to a meeting like this after a long time.
I heard that there is a little more time to come,
I will do my best to be your Saiyan on stage.
Thank you very much.
I haven't actually heard your calls yet.
So I definitely want to hear everyone's call for next year's Tokimeki Natsu no Kirareki stage,
I want to hear all of your calls. I would love to hear all the hand-clapping and everything.
I am so happy to hear your cheers. Thank you very much.
It's like a live performance. I'm having so much fun,
It's so much fun.
Music
This life that can only go on and on and on
It should be a lot of fun, right? Isn't it?
I always believe in the future.
You can't get your hopes up.
Let's go!
Tomorrow Tomorrow is the best theory
Hello to the new you
I don't care what they say
Let's let the heat get the better of us
The strongest theory of "tomorrow tomorrow
Hello to unlimited possibilities
It's not like this, it's a rampant future
I'll say all the things I want to do
Oh! What's that?
We're celebrating!
A youthful Anpanman play!
Ah! It's Sunbubbery!
Thank you for your hard work!Thanks for all your hard work!
Go to Devon and take pictures at strawberries finals.
Thanks for the camaraderie!
Oh no!
Maybe I'm cold.
I'm so happy.
He's so cute.
He's adorable.
That was amazing.
It was so much fun.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to all of you.
Wow! The live outdoor performance was amazing!
It's so mature and powerful.
It was really cool.
The rain forecast is calling for 80% rain.
I'm a sunny girl, sunny girl. I'm a sunny girl.
Terrifying! Upside down!
So cute, upside down!
So, the first day of the Tokyo show is over.
It was so much fun!
I got to hear your voices.
And the sound of these 1000 bands echoed through the air...
It was a wonderful concert!
Thank you very much!
Action
It was the first time for us to play in the "YAGAYAGA" and the first time for us to call out
It was also my first time to call out
The day was getting darker and darker
It's getting darker and darker
It was a lot of fun.
I thought it would be nice to do Memories at night,
The night sky was just perfect.
The night sky was so beautiful.
It was like shooting stars in the sky,
It was wonderful. We still have the Osaka show coming up,
Let's keep up the good work after this!
Thank you very much.
Come on, let's go wherever you want.
Goodbye goodbye, yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets were sparkling
as if my heart was in the sun
I play the rainbow piano
I don't know why, when I smile, the world seems to glow
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, you paint fragments of the future and guide me
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I'll let you play with my tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!